https://www.plasticseurope.org/en/privacy-policy

HomePrivacy policy
Privacy policy
Disclaimer
Terms and conditions of use of the PlasticsEurope web site.
These conditions may be changed at any time.
Protection of personal data
Personal information collected via our website is stored in PlasticsEurope's files. Only the information in the fields of the registration form will be saved in our database.
These data may be processed by PlasticsEurope as part of its customer administration procedures, market research, or customized information and promotional campaigns relating to its products and services. The information you provide may be passed on to companies related to PlasticsEurope.
In accordance with the law on the protection of privacy of 08.12.1992, you have the right to access, and if necessary, rectification, to all of your personal data. You also have the right to oppose the use of your data for free for direct marketing purposes. You can submit your requests for viewing, correction or opposition to info@plasticseurope.org or send them by mail.
Information included
The material contained on this web site is for general information and use only. It does not constitute advice and should not be relied upon in making (or refraining from making) any decision. This content is provided "as is” and “as available”.
PlasticsEurope endeavours to update the information on a regular basis, but it is not claimed to be exhaustive, complete, timely and/or accurate.
PlasticsEurope has compiled the pages on this web site very carefully, and the information placed on this web site is offered in utmost good faith. Nevertheless, PlasticsEurope makes no representations or warranties as to the completeness, timeliness or accuracy of any of this information. Neither PlasticsEurope nor any contributor will be liable for loss or damages of any nature whatsoever resulting from the use of or reliance on the information contained in this web site.
Copyright
This site and its content, including images, where applicable, are subject to the copyright of PlasticsEurope. Reproduction is authorised, except for commercial purposes, provided that the source is mentioned and acknowledged, save where otherwise stated. Where prior permission must be obtained for the reproduction or use of textual and multimedia information (images, sound, software), such permission shall cancel the above-mentioned general permission and shall clearly indicate any restrictions of use. PlasticsEurope claims no copyright on any official document or document in the public domain. Copyright, if any, of third party material found in this site must also be respected.
Trademarks
The PlasticsEurope and "plastics" logos are trademarks registered by PlasticsEurope in Europe. Therefore, these logos/trademarks are subject to the property rights of PlasticsEurope; no rights are granted, except for member companies and National Plastics Associations. The strapline (encompassing key attributes) is available in 14 languages for use across the 28 EU member states plus Norway, Switzerland and Turkey.
Links
Links to other web sites are provided solely as a convenience. Therefore, those links imply neither responsibility for, nor approval of, the information contained in those web sites by PlasticsEurope.
Governing law and jurisdiction
The content of this website, any dispute arising out of the website, and your relationship with us are governed by Belgian law and shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Brussels, Belgium.
Contact us for more information
Contact us for more information about the benefits of plastics and the activities of PlasticsEurope.
Share this page :
In the same category
Stay updated
Sign up for the latest news on plastics and innovation!
Thank you for your subscription
An error occurred during the subscription process. If the problem persists, please contact us: info@plasticseurope.org
An error occurred during the subscription process. If the problem persists, please contact us: info@plasticseurope.org
Close
HomeAbout usWho we areWhat we doMembershipFocus AreasOur commitmentCircular EconomyHealth and SafetyMarine LitterLife Cycle ThinkingInnovationResourcesMarket dataPosition papersPublicationsVideosEco-profilesEducationCP Pallets registrationNewsroomNewsPress releasesUpcoming EventsAbout PlasticsWhat are plasticsPackagingBuilding and ConstructionMobility and TransportElectronicsAgricultureHealthcareSport and LeisureEnergyCareersMembers AreaContactHow to reach usPrivacy policyResearch
